That's two of the three ingredients
I need for the Elixir of Life.
Just one to go:
the purified blood of the demon monarch.
When I go for it,
I'll need to be fully prepared.
I've leveled up a fair bit from
visiting the Demon's Castle.
But officially, I'm still E-Rank.
I might want to get stronger,
but I won't be able to participate
in higher-level raids with that rank.
I need to stop faking.
And it's not like the truth
can stay secret forever.
I'll get my hunter rank reassessed.
The line for hunter rank
assessment is over here.
I wonder what kind of personnel
we'll be able to recruit today.
He looks like a C-Rank.
That one is a pretty obvious E-Rank.
Beyond that...
Yes, this is Baek Yoonho.
This is Hyun Kichul from the
Second Administration Team!
What can I do for you?
He's here!
Say that again?!
I'm sure of it.
Hunter Sung is here to have
his rank reassessed!
Right this way, please.
Sure.
I'm heading there right now.
You don't need to be nervous.
The actual assessment is pretty simple.
I need to get my hunter rank
sorted out so I can earn money.
Maybe then, my ex-wife and
daughter will come back...
Look there.
If you get D-Rank or higher,
the scouts from the guilds will talk to you.
Don't worry. As long as you're not E-Rank,
you can make a good living.
"As long as you're not E-Rank," huh?
Next!
Coming.
If I could get your name for confirmation?
Sung Jinwoo.
A reassessment, then?
Right.
The process is the same as before,
so please hold your hand against
the black crystal and wait.
Huh?
An error?
Pardon me. Could you do it again?
Sure.
That's odd...
Hey, what's the problem?
Chief...
Something's strange. I keep trying,
but it's not able to evaluate him.
That can't be right. Let me see.
See what happens?
Chief?
It's not a malfunction.
It's saying he can't be assessed.
What's that mean?
It means he's got more magic power
than can be measured with this machine!
Huh? That'd mean...
Right. He's the tenth person
ever in the country...
to be S-Rank.
Is there any news on the
winged ants from before?
The intel department's
commenced their necropsy.
They'll be comparing their biology and
trace magic power levels with past examples
in order to see what's going on.
The results will take a bit longer, though.
I see.
So many strange things lately...
Like the red gate, for instance.
Apparently an outsider who was participating
in the White Tiger Guild raid
ended up beating the dungeon boss?
Who exactly is he?
I was present during the investigation,
but not the entire time.
So I don't have all the details.
That's a shame.
Oh, something seems to be
going on over by the lobby.
Most likely an awakened making a fuss
after having been assessed.
I'll check it out.
I'll join you.
I'm curious about the commotion.
He couldn't be assessed?!
Seriously?! I wasn't sure that ever happened!
Never seen anything like it...
Unfortunately, the standard equipment can't properly assess you, Hunter Sung.
Obviously! There's only been
nine hunters like that before.
Would you mind coming back in three days?
Then this guy is the tenth
S-Rank in the country?!
Understood.
It's just like Manager Ahn said!
I need to be the first one to talk to him...
Once that's done,
you'll get your updated license.
Something wrong?
Hey, look!
The head of the Hunters Guild, Choi Jong-in?!
He who stands at the pinnacle of fire magic,
the hunter known as the "ultimate weapon"...
The counterpart to my old nickname.
Well, that explains the commotion, then.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
My name is Choi Jong-in,
and I represent the Hunters Guild.
Have you decided on a guild yet?
I'd like to discuss it with you
if you're not busy.
I am, sorry.
No way!
He just shot Guildmaster Choi down!
Manager Woo, I did mention that I was Choi
Jong-in from the Hunters Guild, didn't I?
Yes, I'm certain.
It seems I've grown conceited.
Hunter Sung... Then it's really true.
And now he's gone without a trace.
Maybe he's an assassin type?
President Baek...
President!
I see how it is now.
The White Tiger's office isn't far from here,
Where is he?!
He left as soon as he exited
the the assessment room!
but he ran hard enough to be short of breath.
I tried to call out to him, but...
That's how badly he wanted to talk to him.
Jackpot. This must be the outsider
who cleared the red gate.
Jong-in.
Of all the people to catch wind of this...
She looks like she could
wake up at any moment.
Just a bit longer now, Mom.
It seems my eyes have failed me all this time.
The surveillance team's job is to watch hunters
and punish any who break the law.
I'm usually confident about
my judgment, but this time...
Do I need surveillance?
Not the same way that a criminal might.
The surveillance team is the only group
able to handle hunter-related incidents.
But when dealing with S-Ranks,
even we're powerless.
There's someone who'd like
to meet you, Hunter Sung.
It's a pleasure.
My name is Go Gunhee, and I'm the
chairman of the Hunter's Association.
First of all, congratulations
on your S-Rank assessment.
The reassessment is but
a formality at this point.
From the moment you're confirmed to be
off the charts, you're S-Rank by definition.
Why bother, then?
With the formal reassessment?
It's something of a grace period.
It allows us to make contact
with individuals such as yourself.
Sadly, despite our reach, the Association
does not have many skilled hunters.
We can't really compete with large guilds
in terms of pay or fame.
Manager Woo is one of our top-level hunters,
and even he's only A-Rank.
I'll get to the point now.
I would be thrilled if you could join us.
I can prepare a key position
in the Association for you.
Why go so far?
The nation's greatest advocates right now
are not the government,
but the hunters, who protect
the people from magic beasts.
The core of which is the five largest guilds.
In a sense, it's like five great dinosaurs
maintaining a delicate stalemate
against each other.
But should you join any of them,
that balance will collapse.
The Hunter's Association is vital
to the nation as a deterrent to them—
a sixth power, essentially.
And that's why you want me to join?
You certainly possess the strength for the job.
Perhaps even one day...
So, what do you think?
It's a good offer.
A job inside of the Association
is basically a guaranteed career track.
I doubt there's anyone with
greater reach than Chairman Go,
especially with the press
and the government.
Plus, he's an amazing hunter.
The first S-Rank to awaken in this country.
He possesses overwhelming magic power
and a physique that's makes it
hard to believe he's over 80.
He's retired, yet he's on even footing
with me after all my efforts to level up.
If I accept his offer, my life will change.
Well, Hunter Sung?
I'm sorry. I have to refuse.
I suppose it all comes down to money, then.
I want to fight, sir.
You mean against magic beasts?
Right. The dungeons are where I belong.
Incredible. I can tell from his eyes
that he's not lying.
How many years has it been
since I've felt this sensation?
I'm impressed my heart can still
make these kinds of noises.
If I were twenty—no, ten years younger,
I could've stood aside someone like him.
Understood. I won't press the issue.
My sister is at home alone,
so I should get going.
Thank you for your time.
I remember how crestfallen I was
when I aged past the point
that even an S-Rank healer
couldn't offset my decline.
Cancel the rest of my schedule for today.
I don't want anything to disrupt this feeling.
Manager Woo, would you join me for a drink?
As long as you don't mind
that I won't partake.
Not a problem.
I wonder if he likes to drink?
The Association mostly handles
D and E-Rank dungeons.
I need to level up as soon as possible
so that I can heal Mom.
I don't have time to waste.
Because I can keep growing!
Come to rub salt in my wounds, Deputy Chief?
Just had questions
I'd like to ask you in person.
This Il-hwan Sung. Is he really a magic beast?
Did he seem like a human to you?
He sure as hell seemed like a beast to me.
All right. Focus on your recovery, then.
Drop by the command center
once you're discharged.
Where is he?!
The command center's tracking him down.
But I doubt they'll be able to bring in
someone who was able to beat you.
Shit!
You'd better stay away from my family.
For your own sake.
If you don't... even death
won't save you from me.
What a humiliating loss...
Even death won't save me?
Is that his idea of a threat?
I know where he's headed.
Now I just need gear.
An artifact that'll let me crush that bastard!
Artifacts: a word that usually
refers to man-made relics.
But in the world of hunters,
artifacts are high-level gear that even
experienced craftsmen can't produce.
With the increase in hunters,
you can find them in online auctions
like anything else, but...
Do they have to be so expensive?
I want my gear to be flawless before
I take on the rest of the Demon's Castle.
Nothing in the store seemed a good fit.
The Sphere of Avarice can be transferred.
I should be able to sell it.
Most of the best gear in circulation offers
a 20-30% increase in performance,
but this sphere can double magic damage.
And that means it'll fetch a high price.
Which will raise the question:
how does an E-Rank like me have it?
People are bound to try and
find out where it came from.
If there was a record of me entering an
A-Rank gate, that'd serve as an excuse.
But I can't join a raid like that as an E-Rank.
Wait, someone's actually recruiting?
This is our data from four years ago?
His photo looks completely
different. Like a child.
Is there a chance he
falsified his original rank?
He's on the record as being
severely injured several times.
That makes it unlikely.
It's incredible that he held out
for so long, after so many raids.
Paying for his mother's Eternal Sleep
treatment and his sister's tuition...
He's been supporting his family
with his income.
You don't see that kind of devotion
from young folks these days.
There's been a report that Hunter Sung
has joined a Hunters Guild raid team.
Then, in spite of what he said, he was
lured in by a lucrative signing bonus...
From what the report says,
he's joined a mining team of theirs.
A mining team?
Yes, sir.
He's certainly hard to predict, isn't he?
So, you're E-Rank?
Yes, sir.
You do much excavation before?
This is my first time.
Then you're a combat type? Shouldn't
have to worry about your fitness, then.
We've got plenty of folks like you, Mr. Sung.
Just relax, and let's work hard!
Right.
Major raids that take place in high-level
dungeons demand a degree of specialization.
You have the strike team
that deals with magic beasts,
the mining team that collects
the mana crystals in the dungeon,
and the collection team that
recovers the beast carcasses.
It's a lot of personnel,
but the profits justify it.
I bet right now, inside the dungeon...
Back up, please.
They don't seem to appreciate the light.
Tanks...
If you would, please.
The carcasses aren't of much use
if they're cooked to well-done,
so I tried to keep it at medium.
I believe that takes care of most
of the nearby enemies.
Let's move on.
I know one of us has a sensitive nose,
so do mind the smell of burning beasts.
The strike team's coming out!
Then everything but the
dungeon boss is dead already?
I could sense he was strong
during our encounter yesterday,
but for everyone to emerge from an
A-Rank gate without a scratch...
just goes to show how strong.
And there's the Hunters Guild
second-in-command.
That's her...
The vice guild master of the Hunters Guild,
and the ninth S-Rank hunter in this country.
Cha Hae-in, the Dancer.
Incredible...
I have to wonder how many people
in the world have that much aura.
I thought I just sensed
something incredible...
Was I imagining it?
For a second, I thought
Chairman Go was around.
But now there's no trace of whoever it was.
She's even sharper than I thought.
All right, everyone! Let's get moving!
All righty...
With the strike team's work finished,
it's the mining and collection teams' turn.
One... two...!
One, two!
It's looking a little loose here!
There's a magic power signal
coming from deeper in the dungeon.
Must be the A-Rank dungeon boss giving it off.
It's stronger than Vulcan and Metis
from the Demon's Castle.
I'm tempted to find out for myself
how strong an A-Rank boss really is.
Did you hear? The guy who joined
for this job is an E-Rank.
E-Rank? Are you kidding me?
What the hell was the boss thinking?
No matter where you go,
E-Ranks get the same treatment.
Not that I intend on doing this for long.
Come on, let's get a move on!
It's tight enough in here!
You can't just stand around—
Uh, well... P-Please take your time.
Is that dude seriously E-Rank?
Chief... Is he really E-Rank?
Yeah.
He seems... super strong, though?
I get the feeling Mr. Sung is God's gift
to blue-collars like us.
Okay, break time.
Let's all go get something to eat.
Right.
You coming, Mr. Sung?
I just want to finish up here first.
Understood.
Don't go too far in, though.
Sure.
I'm finally alone.
I can't let this chance slip by.
Break time lasts an hour... Let's take a peek.
This must be the boss chamber.
Definitely seems stronger than Metis.
I realize that I shouldn't defeat this boss.
If I do, the gate closes,
at a huge loss to the Hunters Guild.
Still... A little poke can't hurt.
What are you doing there?
I'll ask again.
What do you think you're doing?